1. openBrowser("https://iddtrain.georgiacollaborative.com/IDDPortal/")
5. navigateToUrl("https://iddtrain.georgiacollaborative.com/IDDPortal/")
9. maximizeWindow()
13. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/1_Page_HomePage to Login/input__username"), "Test123")
17. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/1_Page_HomePage to Login/input__password"), "Password123")
21. Thread.sleep(3000)
25. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/1_Page_HomePage to Login/button_Login"))
29. Thread.sleep(2000)
33. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/2_Page_Welcome/b_Submit a New Application"))
37. Thread.sleep(2000)
41. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/3_Page_TermsAndConditions/div_httpsgadbhdd.policystat.co"))
45. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/3_Page_TermsAndConditions/button_Proceed with online app"))
49. Thread.sleep(2000)
55. Start of General Page
59. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input__lName"), "LastName")
63. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input__dob"), "01/01/1990")
67. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/label_Select_Gender"))
71. Thread.sleep(2000)
75. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/li_Male"))
79. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/label_Select_MaritalStatus"))
83. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/li_Married"))
87. Thread.sleep(2000)
91. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/label_Select_Race"))
95. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/li_WhiteCaucasian"))
99. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/label_Select_Hispanic"))
103. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/li_No"))
107. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input__SSN"), "800-10-0101")
111. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/label_Select_CurrentLivingArrangements"))
115. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/li_Community living arrangemen"))
119. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input__pphoneNumber"), "(111) 111-1111")
125. Enter Street Address
129. Thread.sleep(1000)
133. sendKeys(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input__generalStreetPrimary_pr"), Keys.chord(ARROW_DOWN, ENTER))
137. Thread.sleep(1000)
141. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input_Yes_law (1)"))
145. Thread.sleep(1000)
149. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/input_No_veteran (1)"))
153. Thread.sleep(1000)
157. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/CheckhereifMailingAddressisSame"))
161. Thread.sleep(1000)
165. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 1/button_Next Page"), 0)
171. End of General Information Page 1
177. Start of General info Page 2/2
181. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/input__pFName"), "PrimaryName")
185. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/input__pLName"), "PrimaryLastName")
189. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/label_Enter Relationship"))
193. Thread.sleep(1000)
197. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/span_Case Worker"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
201. sendKeys(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/label_Enter Relationship"), Keys.chord(ARROW_DOWN, ARROW_DOWN, ENTER))
205. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/input__pAge"), "30")
209. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/input__ppphoneNumber"), "2111111111")
213. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/div_Check here if the primary"))
217. Thread.sleep(1000)
221. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/4_Page_GeneralInformation/General info Page 2/button_Next Page"))
227. Start of Legal Status and Guardian Page
231. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/5_Legal Status and Guardian/Span in the dropdown"))
235. Thread.sleep(1000)
241. End of Legal Status and Guardian Page
245. Thread.sleep(1000)
249. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/label_Select"))
253. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/label_Select - Value"))
257. Thread.sleep(1000)
261. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/No- other than English"))
265. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/Communicated Verbally"))
269. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/label_Select - Preferred Mode of Communication"))
273. Thread.sleep(2000)
279. Add Send Keys here
283. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/label_Select - Value - Preferred Mode of Communication"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
287. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/input_No_applicantdeaf"))
291. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/input_No_applicantdeaf- 2nd radio"))
295. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/input_No_Vision Radio 1"))
299. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/6_Page_Communication, Hearing and Vision/input_No_Vision Radio 2"))
305. End of Communication, Hearing and Vision
309. Thread.sleep(2000)
315. Start of IDD Diagonosis, Resources & Referrals
319. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/7_Page_IDD Diagonosis Resources and Referrals/div_Choose"))
323. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/7_Page_IDD Diagonosis Resources and Referrals/Label_Access_Crisis Line"))
327. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/7_Page_IDD Diagonosis Resources and Referrals/div_Current Resource Selection"))
331. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/7_Page_IDD Diagonosis Resources and Referrals/Label_Adoption Assistance"))
335. sendKeys(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/7_Page_IDD Diagonosis Resources and Referrals/input__pReferral Income"), "50000")
341. End of Page IDD Diagonosis, Resources and Referrals
347. Start of Physician Page
351. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/input__pPhysician Name"), "Hopkins")
355. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/input__pCity"), "Fort Smith")
359. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/label_Enter State"))
363. Thread.sleep(2000)
367. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/Span_State - Arkansas"))
371. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/input__pZip code"), "30346")
375. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/input__pPhone Number"), "2111111111")
379. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/8_Physician Details/div_Save Button"))
383. Thread.sleep(1000)
389. End of Physician Page
395. Start of Application Supporting Document
399. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/9_Application Supporting Documents/label_Document Type"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
403. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/9_Application Supporting Documents/li_Birth Certificate"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
407. Thread.sleep(5000)
411. actions = new org.openqa.selenium.interactions.Actions(com.kms.katalon.core.webui.driver.DriverFactory.getWebDriver())
415. actions.moveToElement(findWebElement(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/9_Application Supporting Documents/div_Choose File"), 30))
419. actions.sendKeys("C:\\Users\\mitali.p.shah\\Downloads\\Test.docx")
423. build().perform()
427. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/9_Application Supporting Documents/div_Upload"))
431. Thread.sleep(1000)
437. End of Application Supporting Documents
441. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/input__fName"), "Applicant Name")
445. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/input__lName"), "Applicant Last Name")
449. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/label_Application completed by"))
453. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/label_Method of Contact"))
457. setText(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/input__pphoneNumber"), "2111111111")
461. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/div_I certify"))
465. click(findTestObject("Submit Application/Page_Online Application for Intelle/10_Application Signature/button_Submit Application"))